A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of the Medical Letter publication, 1986-1995 FA1103
Rockefeller Archive Center
- TML, 31-110 - Malathion - Malathion for head lice, 1989 December 15 (Box 45, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 32-1 - Hepatitis - Interferon for chronic viral hepatitis, 1990 January 12 (Box 45, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 32-3 - Clozapine - Clozapine for schizophrenia, 1990 January 12 (Box 45, Folder 15-18)
- TML, 32-5 - Sexually transmitted diseases - Treatment of sexually transmitted diseases, 1990 January 26 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- TML, 32-5 - Sexually transmitted diseases - Treatment of sexually transmitted diseases, 1990 January 26 (Box 46, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 32-11 - HIV - Drugs for HIV Infections, 1990 February 9 (Box 46, Folder 5-9)
- TML, 32-13 - Mefloquine for malaria; and TML, 32-98 - Mefloquine, 1990 February 9 and October 19 (Box 46, Folder 10-12)
- TML, 32-15 - Anistreplase for acute coronary thrombosis, 1990 February 23 (Box 46, Folder 13-16)
- TML, 32-17 - Pressure ulcers - Treatment of pressure ulcers, 1990 February 23 (Box 46, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 32-17 - Pressure ulcers - Treatment of pressure ulcers, 1990 February 23 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- TML, 32-19 - Omeprazole, 1990 March 9 (Box 47, Folder 2-6)
- TML, 32-21 - Permathrin for scabies, 1990 March 9 (Box 47, Folder 7-8)
- TML, 32-22 - Propofol, 1990 March 9 (Box 47, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 32-23 - Parasitic infections - Drugs for parasitic infections, 1990 March 23 (Box 47, Folder 13-17)
- TML, 32-33 - Immunization - Advice for travelers, 1990 April 6 (Box 48, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 32-37 - Propefenone - Propefenone for cardiac arrythmias, 1990 April 20 (Box 48, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 32-38 - Desmopressn for nocturnal enuresis, 1990 April 20 (Box 48, Folder 9-10)
- TML, 32-39 - Benzodiazepines, 1990 April 20 (Box 48, Folder 11-14)
- TML, 32-41 - Antimircobials - The choice of antimicrobial drugs, 1990 May 4 (Box 48, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 32-41 - Antimircobials - The choice of antimicrobial drugs, 1990 May 4 (Box 49, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 32-49 - Cancer chemotherapy - Advujant chemotherapy of early breast cancer, 1990 May 18 (Box 49, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 32-50 - Fluconazole, 1990 May 18 (Box 49, Folder 7-11)
- TML, 32-53 - Antidepressants, tricyclic - Sudden death in children treated with tricyclic antidepressant, 1990 June 1 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- TML, 32-54 - Immunization - Routine immunization for adults, 1990 June 1 (Box 49, Folder 13-14)
- TML, 32-57 - Fat substitutes, 1990 June 15 (Box 49, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 32-58 - Fungal infections - Drugs for treatment of fungal infections, 1990 June 15 (Box 49, Folder 18-19)
- TML, 32-58 - Fungal infections - Drugs for treatment of fungal infections, 1990 June 15 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- TML, 32-61 - Betaxolol - Betaxolol for hypertension, 1990 June 29 (Box 50, Folder 2-4)
- TML, 32-63 - Adenosine, 1990 June 29 (Box 50, Folder 5-7)
- TML, 32-64 - Balloon dilatation of the prostate, 1990 June 29 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- TML, 32-65 - Cephalosporins - Cefmetazole sodium (Zefazone), 1990 July 13 (Box 50, Folder 9-10)
- TML, 32-66 - Environmental health - Treatment of heat injury, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 11-12)
- TML, 32-69 - Eye - Soft contact lenses, 1990 July 27 (Box 50, Folder 13-14)
- TML, 32-70 - Gonadotropins - Gonadorelin for induction of ovulation, 1990 July 27 (Box 50, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 32-73 - Viral Infections - Drugs for viral infections; and TML 32-90 - Encephalitis, 1990 August 10 and September 21 (Box 50, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 32-73 - Viral Infections - Drugs for viral infections; and TML 32-90 - Encephalitis, 1990 August 10 and September 21 (Box 51, Folder 1-5)
- TML, 32-79 - Ketorolac - Ketorolac tromethamine, 1990 August 24 (Box 51, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 32-81 - Nafarelin - Nafarelin for endometriosis, 1990 August 24 (Box 51, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 32-83 - Fluoxetine - Fluoxetine (Prozac) revisited; and TML, 32-106 - Correction - Fluoxetiine interaction, 1990 September 7 and November 16 (Box 51, Folder 12-15)
- TML, 32-85 - Interleukin-2, 1990 September 7 (Box 51, Folder 16-20)
- TML, 32-87 - Pegademase, 1990 September 21 (Box 52, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 32-88 - Pulmonary toxicity - Drugs that cause pulmonary toxicity, 1990 September 21 (Box 52, Folder 3-7)
- TML, 32-91 - Metipranolol - a new beta-blocker for glaucoma, 1990 October 5 (Box 52, Folder 8-9)
- TML, 32-95 - Dexocine, 1990 October 19 (Box 52, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 32-99 - Moricizine - Moricizine for cardiac arrhythmias, 1990 November 2 (Box 52, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 32-100 - Botulimum toxin - Botulinum toxin for ocular muscle disorders, 1990 November 2 (Box 52, Folder 15-18)
- TML, 32-102 - Goserelin - another LH-RH analog for prostate cancer, 1990 November 2 (Box 53, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 32-103 - Poison and Poisoning - Prevention and treatment of nerve gas poisoning, 1990 November 16 (Box 53, Folder 5-6)
- TML, 32-105 - Olsalazine - Olsalazine for ulcerative colitis, 1990 November 16 (Box 53, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 32-107 - Cephalosporins - Choice of cephalosporins, 1990 November 30 (Box 53, Folder 10-13)
- TML, 32-111 - Etidronate - Etidronate for postmenopausal osteoporosis, 1990 December 14 (Box 53, Folder 14-15)
- TML, 32-92 - Addiction - Acute reactions to drugs of abuse, 1990 October 5 (Box 53, Folder 16-19)
- TML, 32-112 - Mifepristone (RU 486), 1990 December 14 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- TML, 32-112 - Mifepristone (RU 486), 1990 December 14 (Box 54, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 32-114 - Pipercuronium - a new neuromuscular blocker, 1990 December 14 (Box 54, Folder 5-6)
- TML, 32-115 - Laparoscopic Cholecystectomy, 1990 December 28 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- TML, 32-116 - Impotence - Intracavernous injections for impotence, 1990 December 28 (Box 54, Folder 8-9)
- TML, 32-117 - Rabies vaccine, 1990 December 28 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- TML, 32-96 - Diagnostic tests - Desktop systems for office chemistries, 1990 October 19 (Box 54, Folder 11-14)
- TML, 32-71 - Trimethoprim-polymyxin B for bacterial conjunctivitis, 1990 July 27 (Box 54, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 32-23 - Parasitic infections - Drugs for parasitic infections, 1990 March 23 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- TML, 32-23 - Parasitic infections - Drugs for parasitic infections, 1990 March 23 (Box 55, Folder 1-3)
- TML - Drugs and Food, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 4-9)
- TML - Special Publications - Handbook of Antimicrobial Therapy (Revised Edition), 1990 (Box 55, Folder 10-15)
- TML, 32-2 - Pulmonary Surfactants - Premature infants with respiratory distress, 1990 January 12 (Box 55, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 32-86 - Influenza vaccine, 1990-1991, 1990 September 7 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- TML, 33-1 - Choice of Lipid Lowering drugs, 1991 January 11 (Box 56, Folder 1-6)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted material - Open in 2017
- TML, 33-5 - H. Influenza vaccine for Infants, 1991 January 25 (Box 56, Folder 7-12)
- TML, 33-8 - Gamma hydroxy butyrate poisoning, 1991 January 25 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- TML, 33-9 - Drugs for ambulatory asthma, 1991 February 8 (Box 56, Folder 14-18)
- TML, 33-7 - Laser coronary angioplasty, 1991 January 25 (Box 57, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 33-13 - Health problems in the Persian Gulf, 1991 February 22 (Box 57, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 33-15 - Doxazosin for hypertension, 1991 February 22 (Box 57, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 33-17 - A Subdermal Progestin Implant for Long-Term Contraception, 1991 March 8 (Box 57, Folder 10-13)
- TML, 33-18 - Pravastatin and Simvastatin for Hypercholesterolemania, 1991 March 8 (Box 57, Folder 14-18)
- TML, 33-29 - BCG for Bladder Cancer, 1991 April 5 (Box 57, Folder 19-21)
- TML, 33-21 - Drugs for cancer chemotherapy, 1991 March 22 (Box 58, Folder 1-7)
- TML, 33-30 - Alprazolam for panic disorder, 1991 April 5 (Box 58, Folder 8-11)
- TML, 33-32 - Safe needles, 1991 April 5 (Box 58, Folder 12-13)
- TML, 33-33 - Drugs for hypertension; and TML, 33-64 - Hypertension - Correction, 1991 April 19 and June 28 (Box 58, Folder 14-18)
- TML, 33-33 - Drugs for hypertension; and TML, 33-64 - Hypertension - Correction, 1991 April 19 and June 28 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- TML, 33-39 - Autologous bone marrow transplantation for advanced breast cancer, 1991 May 3 (Box 59, Folder 2-3)
- TML, 33-40 - Rapid diagnostic tests for group A strepococcal pharyngitis, 1991 May 3 (Box 59, Folder 4-8)
- TML, 33-41 - Gallium for hypercalcemia of malignancy, 1991 May 3 (Box 59, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 33-43 - Drugs for pshchiatric disorders, 1991 May 17 (Box 59, Folder 13-18)
- TML, 33-45 - Isradipidine for hypertension, 1991 May 31 (Box 59, Folder 19)
- TML, 33-45 - Isradipidine for hypertension, 1991 May 31 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
- TML. 33-52 - Opthalmic ciprofloxacin, 1991 May 31 (Box 60, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 33-53 - Bepridil for angina pectoris; and TML, 33-74 - Bepridil - Correction, 1991 May 31 and July 26 (Box 60, Folder 5-7)
- TML, 33-55 - Drugs for cardiac arrhythmias, 1991 June 14 (Box 60, Folder 8-12)
- TML, 33-61 - Granulocyte colony-stimulating factors, 1991 June 28 (Box 60, Folder 13-17)
- TML, 33-63 - Ondansetron to prevent vomiting after cancer chemotherapy, 1991 June 28 (Box 60, Folder 18-19)
- TML, 33-63 - Ondansetron to prevent vomiting after cancer chemotherapy, 1991 June 28 (Box 61, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 33-65 - Drugs for rheumatoid arthritis, 1991 July 12 (Box 61, Folder 4-9)
- TML, 33-71 - Ofloxacin, 1991 July 26 (Box 61, Folder 10-15)
- TML, 33-73 - Doxacurium, 1991 July 26 (Box 61, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 33-75 - Intravenous Ciprofloxacin, 1991 August 9 (Box 61, Folder 18-19)
- TML, 33-76 - Altremine for ovarian cancer, 1991 August 9 (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 33-78 - Succimer - an oral drug for lead poisoning, 1991 August 9 (Box 62, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 33-79 - Etodolac, 1991 August 23 (Box 62, Folder 5-9)
- TML, 33-81 - Topical drugs for vaginal candidiasis, 1991 August 23 (Box 62, Folder 10-12)
- TML, 33-82 - Algucerase for Gaucher's disease, 1991 August 23 (Box 62, Folder 13-14)
- TML, 33-83 - Three new ACE inhibitors for hypertension, 1991 September 6 (Box 62, Folder 15-20)
- TML, 33-84 - Idarubicin, 1991 September 6 (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 33-85 - Dexrazoxane, 1991 September 6 (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 33-89 - Fludarabine, 1991 September 20 (Box 63, Folder 5-6)
- TML, 33-91 - Estazolam - A new benzodiazepine hypnotic, 1991 October 4 (Box 63, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 33-92 - Sinemet CR for Parkinson's disease, 1991 October 4 (Box 63, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 33-94 - FK 506 - An investigational immunosuppressant, 1991 October 4 (Box 63, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 33-95 - Drugs for AIDS and associated infections, 1991 October 18 (Box 63, Folder 15-19)
- TML, 33-95 - Drugs for AIDS and associated infections, 1991 October 18 (Box 64, Folder 1-8)
- TML, 33-103 - Monoclonal antibodies for Gram-Negative sepsis, 1991 November 1 (Box 64, Folder 9-10)
- TML, 33-104 - Laser treatment of cutaneous vascular lesions, 1991 November 1 (Box 64, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 33-107 - Prevention and treatment of cholera, 1991 November 15 (Box 64, Folder 14-15)
- TML, 33-108 - Topical corticosteroids, 1991 November 15 (Box 64, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 33-111 - Drugs for treatment of peptic ulcers, 1991 November 29 (Box 65, Folder 1-5)
- TML, 33-115 - Felodipine - another calcium-channel blocker for hypertension, 1991 December 13 (Box 65, Folder 6-9)
- TML, 33-87 - New ways to scan the myocardium, 1991 September 20 (Box 65, Folder 10-17)
- TML, 33-115 - Intranasal triamcinolone for allergic rhinitis, 1991 December 13 (Box 66, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 33-117 - Podofilox for genital warts, 1991 December 13 (Box 66, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 33-119 - Drugs for sexually transmitted diseases, 1991 December 27 (Box 66, Folder 5-9)
- TML (European Edition) - Cetirizine, 1991 May 29 (Box 66, Folder 10-12)
- TML (European Edition) - Dexfenfluramine, 1991 July 2 (Box 66, Folder 13-14)
- TML (European Edition) - Zolipidem for insomnia, 1991 December 14 (Box 66, Folder 15-16)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice from the Medical Letter (Revised Edition), 1991 (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice from the Medical Letter (Revised Edition) - Parkinson's disease, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 3-4)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice from the Medical Letter (Revised Edition) - Choice of Contraceptives, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 5-7)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice from the Medical Letter (Revised Edition) - Drugs for Migraine, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 8-10)
- TML, 33-86 - Influenza vaccine, 1991-1992, 1991 September 6 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- TML, 34-1 - Pamidronate, 1992 January 10 (Box 68, Folder 1-3)
  Restricted material - Open in 2018
- TML, 34-3 - Foscarnet, 1992 January 10 (Box 68, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 34-5 - Antimicrobial prophylaxis in surgery, 1992 January 24 (Box 68, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 34-9 - Safety of terfenadine and astemizole, 1992 February 7 (Box 68, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 34-10 - Drugs for tuberculosis, 1992 February 7 (Box 68, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 34-13 - Reading machines for the blind, 1992 February 21 (Box 68, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 34-14 - Drugs for treatment of fungal infections, 1992 February 21 (Box 68, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 34-14 - Drugs for treatment of fungal infections, 1992 February 21 (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 34-27 - Quinapril for hypertension, 1992 March 20 (Box 69, Folder 3-5)
- TML, 34-28 - Trentinoin for photo-damaged skin, 1992 March 20 (Box 69, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 34-20 - Drug treatment for cardiac arrest, 1992 March 20 (Box 69, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 34-31 - Drugs for viral infections, 1992 April 3 (Box 69, Folder 13-17)
- TML, 34-31 - Drugs for viral infections, 1992 April 3 (Box 70, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 34-37 - Smoking - Nicotine patches, 1992 April 17 (Box 70, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 34-38 - Nambutone - a new NSAID, 1992 April 17 (Box 70, Folder 7-10)
- TML, 34-45 - Clarithromycin and azithromycin, 1992 May 15 (Box 70, Folder 11-15)
- TML, 34-47 - Sertraline for treatment of depression, 1992 May 15 (Box 70, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 34-47 - Sertraline for treatment of depression, 1992 May 15 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- TML, 34-49 - The choice of antibacterial drugs; and TML, 34-110 - Correction, 1992 May 29 and November 27 (Box 71, Folder 2-5)
- TML, 34-57 - Pravastatin, simvastatin, and lovastatin for lowering cholesterol concentrations, 1992 June 12 (Box 71, Folder 6-7)
- TML, 34-61 - Isosorbide mononitrate for angina, 1992 June 26 (Box 71, Folder 8-11)
- TML, 34-62 - Capsaicin - a topical analgesic, 1992 June 26 (Box 71, Folder 12-15)
- TML, 34-63 - Cefprozil, 1992 June 26 (Box 71, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 34-63 - Cefprozil, 1992 June 26 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- TML, 34-65 - Ticlopidine for prevention of stroke, 1992 July 10 (Box 72, Folder 2-4)
- TML, 34-73 - Drugs that cause sexual dysfunction, 1992 August 7 (Box 72, Folder 5-13)
- TML, 34-79 - Bone marrow transplants for malignant diseases, 1992 August 21 (Box 72, Folder 14-17)
- TML, 34-80 - Oral mesalamine for ulcerative colitis, 1992 August 21 (Box 72, Folder 18)
- TML, 34-80 - Oral mesalamine for ulcerative colitis, 1992 August 21 (Box 73, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 34-82 - Mivacurium - a new neuromuscular blocker, 1992 August 21 (Box 73, Folder 4-5)
- TML, 34-84 - High altitude sickness, 1992 September 4 (Box 73, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 34-87 - Loracarbef, 1992 September 18 (Box 73, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 34-89 - Pentostatin and 2-chlorodeoxyadenosine for hairy-cell leukemia, 1992 September 18 (Box 73, Folder 12-15)
- TML, 34-90 - Influenza vaccine, 1992-1993, 1992 September 18 (Box 73, Folder 16)
- TML, 34-91 - Sumatriptan for migraine, 1992 October 2 (Box 73, Folder 17-20)
- TML, 34-93 - Prostate specific antigen, 1992 October 2 (Box 73, Folder 21)
- TML, 34-93 - Prostate specific antigen, 1992 October 2 (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 34-95 - Treatment of lyme disease, 1992 October 16 (Box 74, Folder 3-6)
- TML, 34-97 - Transdermal fentanyl, 1992 October 16 (Box 74, Folder 7-8)
- TML, 34-99 - Amlodipine - a new calcium-channel blocker, 1992 October 20 (Box 74, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 34-101 - Choice of drugs for postmenopausal osteoporosis, 1992 October 30 (Box 74, Folder 13-15)
- TML, 34-103 - Enoxacin - a new fluroquinolone, 1992 November 13 (Box 74, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 34-105 - Tenoposide for acute lymphoblastic leukemia, 1992 November 13 (Box 75, Folder 1-5)
- TML, 34-107 - Cefpodoxime proxetil - a new oral cephalosporin, 1992 November 27 (Box 75, Folder 6-7)
- TML, 34-109 - Topical treatment for bacterial vaginosis, 1992 November 27 (Box 75, Folder 8-9)
- TML, 34-111 - Choice of contraceptives, 1992 December 11 (Box 75, Folder 10-14)
- TML, 34-115 - Meters for glucose monitoring, 1992 December 25 (Box 75, Folder 15-16)
- TML (European Edition) - Nedocromil for asthma, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 17-18)
- TML (European Edition) - Nedocromil for asthma, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 1-2)
- TML (European Edition) - Moclomide for treatment of depression, 1992 August 14 (Box 76, Folder 3-5)
- TML (European Edition) - Bisphophonates, 1992 January 6 (Box 76, Folder 6-7)
- TML - Special Publications - Handbook of Antimicrobial Therapy, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 8-10)
- TML - Special Publications - Handbook of Antimicrobial Therapy - Routine Immunization, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 34-71 - Flecainide for supraventricular tachyarrhythmias, 1992 July 24 (Box 76, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 34-116 - Intravenous immune globulin, 1992 December 25 (Box 76, Folder 17)
- TML, 34-116 - Intravenous immune globulin, 1992 December 25 (Box 77, Folder 1-5)
- TML, 34-83 - Finasteride for benign prostatic hypertrophy, 1992 September 4 (Box 77, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 34-69 - New recommendations for immunization against pertusis, 1992 July 24 (Box 77, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 34-41 - Advice for travelers, 1992 May 1 (Box 77, Folder 12-15)
- TML, 34-66 - Flumanzil, 1992 July 10 (Box 77, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 34-66 - Flumanzil, 1992 July 10 (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
- TML (European Edition) - Teicoplanin, 1992 July 2 (Box 78, Folder 3-5)
- TML, 34-64 - Two new fluroquinolones, 1992 June 26 (Box 78, Folder 6-10)
- TML, Drugs of Choice - Epilepsy (Revised Edition), 1991 (Box 78, Folder 11-15)
- TML, 35-1 - Drugs for pain, 1993 January 8 (Box 79, Folder 1-5)
  Restricted material - Open in 2019
- TML, 35-7 - Itraconazole, 1993 January 22 (Box 79, Folder 6-10)
- TML, 35-9 - New advertisements for old antihistamine, 1993 January 22 (Box 79, Folder 11-12)
- TML, 35-11 - Drugs for ambulatory asthma, 1993 February 5 (Box 79, Folder 13-17)
- TML, 35-11 - Drugs for ambulatory asthma, 1993 February 5 (Box 80, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 35-15 - Oxaprozin for arthritis, 1993 February 19 (Box 80, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 35-16 - Update on clozapine, 1993 February 19 (Box 80, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 35-19 - Choice of cholesterol-lowering drugs, 1993 March 19 (Box 80, Folder 13-17)
- TML, 35-19 - Choice of cholesterol-lowering drugs, 1993 March 19 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- TML, 35-23 - Flosequinan for heart failure, 1993 March 19 (Box 81, Folder 2-4)
- TML, 35-24 - Paroxetine for treatment of depression, 1993 March 19 (Box 81, Folder 5-7)
- TML, 35-25 - Choice of an antidepressant, 1993 March 19 (Box 81, Folder 8-10)
- TML, 35-27 - Sotalol for cardiac arrhythmias, 1993 April 2 (Box 81, Folder 11-15)
- TML, 35-28 - Atovaquone for pneumocystis carini pneumonia, 1993 April 2 (Box 81, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 35-29 - Galactodosidarse to prevent gas, 1993 April 2 (Box 82, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 35-31 - Drugs for Parkinson's disease, 1993 April 16 (Box 82, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 35-35 - Zolpidem for insomnia, 1993 April 30 (Box 82, Folder 5-7)
- TML, 35-36 - Rifabutin, 1993 April 30 (Box 82, Folder 8-10)
- TML, 35-38 - Desflurane - a new volatile anesthestic, 1993 April 30 (Box 82, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 35-39 - Pacilitaxel (taxol) for ovarian cancer, 1993 April 30 (Box 82, Folder 14-17)
- TML, 35-40 - Drugs for chronic heart failure, 1993 May 14 (Box 82, Folder 18)
- TML, 35-40 - Drugs for chronic heart failure, 1993 May 14 (Box 83, Folder 1-5)
- TML, 35-43 - Drugs for cancer chemotherapy, 1993 May 28 (Box 83, Folder 6-11)
- TML, 35-51 - Recombinant antihemophilic factor, 1993 June 11 (Box 83, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 35-52 - Oncoscint for detection of disseminated colorectal and ovarian cancer, 1993 June 11 (Box 83, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 35-53 - Shade Uvaguard - a second broad-spectrum sunscreen, 1993 June 11 (Box 84, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 35-55 - Drugs for hypertension; and TML, 35-98 - Correction, 1993 June 25 and October 15 (Box 84, Folder 3-8)
- TML, 35-61 - Interferon beta-1B for multiple sclerosis, 1993 July 9 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- TML, 35-63 - Insect venom immunotherapy, 1993 July 9 (Box 84, Folder 10-14)
- TML, 35-65 - Drugs that cause psychiatric symptoms, 1993 July 23 (Box 84, Folder 15-19)
- TML, 35-65 - Drugs that cause psychiatric symptoms, 1993 July 23 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- TML, 35-71 - Loratadine - a new antihistamine, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 2-5)
- TML, 35-72 -Drugs for acute spinal chord injury, 1993 August 6 (Box 85, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 35-73 - Desogestrel - a new progestin for oral contraception, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 35-75 - Enoxaparin - a low-molecular-weight heparin (Box 85, Folder 13-16)
- TML, 35-76 - Topical terbinafine for tinea infections, 1993 August 20 (Box 85, Folder 17)
- TML, 35-76 - Topical terbinafine for tinea infections, 1993 August 20 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- TML, 35-79 - Drugs for AIDS and associated infections, 1993 September 17 (Box 86, Folder 2-12)
- TML, 35-87 - Tacrine for Alzheimer's disease, 1993 September 17 (Box 86, Folder 13-15)
- TML, 35-89 - Influenza vaccine, 1993-1994, 1993 September 17 (Box 86, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 35-91 - Antimicrobial prophylaxis in surgery, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 18)
- TML, 35-91 - Antimicrobial prophylaxis in surgery, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 35-95 - Corneal surgery for myopia, 1993 October 15 (Box 87, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 35-97 - Masoprocol for multiple actinic keratoses, 1993 October 15 (Box 87, Folder 9-10)
- TML, 35-99 - Drugs for tuberculosis, 1993 October 29 (Box 87, Folder 11-14)
- TML, 35-102 - Radioactive strontium-89 for painful bone metastases, 1993 October 29 (Box 87, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 35-103 - Surgical treatment of Parkinson's disease, 1993 November 12 (Box 87, Folder 18-19)
- TML, 35-103 - Surgical treatment of Parkinson's disease, 1993 November 12 (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 35-104 - Tetramune - a combined vaccine for infants, 1993 November 12 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- TML, 35-105 - Butorphanol nasal spray for pain, 1993 November 12 (Box 88, Folder 4-5)
- TML, 35-107 - Felbamate, 1993 November 26 (Box 88, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 35-107 - Rimantadine for prevention and treatment of influenza, 1993 November 26 (Box 88, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 35-111 - Drugs for parasitic infections, 1993 December 10 (Box 88, Folder 12-19)
- TML, 35-111 - Drugs for parasitic infections, 1993 December 10 (Box 89, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 35-123 - The female condom, 1993 December 24 (Box 89, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 35-124 - Drugs for vomiting caused by cancer chemotherapy, 1993 December 24 (Box 89, Folder 7-10)
- TML (European Edition) - Curosurf, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 11-12)
- TML (European Edition) - Iloprost, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 13-14)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice - Drugs for Migraine, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 15-16)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice - Drugs for Peptic Ulcers, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 17-19)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice - Drugs for psychiatric disorders, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 1-6)
- TML (European Edition) - Terbinafine, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice - Drugs for rheumatoid arthritis, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 8-11)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice - Drugs for cardiac arrhythmias, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 12-16)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice - Drugs for epilepsy, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 17)
- TML, 36-1 - Drugs for sexually transmitted diseases, 1994 January 7 (Box 91, Folder 1-7)
  Restricted material - Open in 2020
- TML, 36-7 - Piperaillin-Tazobactam, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- TML, 36-9 - Topical minoxidil for baldness - a reappraisal, 1994 January 21 (Box 91, Folder 9-12)